adviacu.org 2016-12-03

# 

ADVIA CREDIT UNION MEMBER PRIVACY NOTICE
FACTS                              WHAT DOES ADVIA CREDIT UNION DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL
                                   INFORMATION?
                                   Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
Why?                               consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how
                                   we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to
                                   understand what we do.
                                   The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have
What?                              with us. This information can include:
                                          Social Security Number
                                          Transaction history, account balances and payment history
                                          Credit history and credit scores
                                   When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this
                                   notice.
                                   All financial companies need to share member/customers’ personal information to run their
How?                               everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their
                                   customers’ personal information; the reasons the credit union chooses to share; and whether you
                                   can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information                          Does the credit union            Can you limit this
                                                                        share?                           sharing?
For our everyday business purposes – such as to process your            YES                              NO
transactions, maintain your accounts, respond to court orders
and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes – to offer our products and services         YES                              YES
to you
For joint marketing with other financial companies                      YES                              YES
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information            YES                              YES
about your transactions and experiences
For our affiliates’ every day business purposes – information           NO                               N/A
about your credit worthiness
For our affiliates to market to you                                     YES                              YES
For Non Affiliates to market to you                                     YES                              YES
                                                           Call 844-238-4228 or go to www.adviacu.org
Questions?
Who are we
Who is providing this notice?                              Advia Credit Union
What we do
How does the credit union protect my personal              To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we
information?                                               use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include
                                                           computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does the credit union collect my personal              We collect your personal information, for example, when you
information?                                                     Open and account or deposit money
                                                                 Pay your bills or apply for a loan
                                                                 Use your credit or debit card
Why can’t I limit all sharing?                             Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                                                 Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information
                                                                    about your creditworthiness
                                                                 Affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                                                 Sharing for non-affiliates to market to you
                                                           State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit
                                                           sharing

Definitions
Affiliates                                             Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial
                                                       and nonfinancial companies.
                                                        Advia Financial Advisors (CUNA Mutual Brokerage Services, Inc.)
                                                        Mortgage Center
Non-affiliates                                         Companies not already related by common ownership or control. They can
                                                       be financial and nonfinancial companies (may vary regionally)
                                                        Credit Union National Association (CUNA)
                                                        CUNA Mutual Group
Joint marketing                                        A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together
                                                       market financial products or services to you
Other important information
Please contact us with questions or concerns at our Main Office Location: 550 South Riverview; Parchment, MI 49004. Phone 844-
238-4228.
